Guide to the Grace A. Kempton and Willet Main Kempton Family Papers M2004
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Third and Final Report to the Secretary of the Navy (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Lt. Grace A. Kempton Personal Affair Division (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Transmittal Slip (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Morale Program 1944 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Manual Explanatory of the Priviledges, Rights, and Benefits... (Box 17, Folder 10)
- War Department Bureau of Public Relations (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Various Manuscripts (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Information and Education Division letter from Grace Kempton to Donna Niles (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Hq. 41st Division Far Pacific (Box 17, Folder 14)
- The Post Record (Box 17, Folder 15)
- The Army Nurse (Box 17, Folder 16)
- The War in Outline (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Second Report of the Commanding General of the Army Air Forces to the Secretary of War (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Meet our New Director (Box 17, Folder 19)
- War Department Bureau of Public Relations Press Release (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Hamilton Field, California, Saturday 3 March 1945 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- An Urgent War Message to Patriotic Americans The Army Needs your Help (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Bulletin of Information Women's Interest Section (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Medal 1914 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Guide to the Information Materials September 1944 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Statement by the Secretary of War May 10, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Hospital Ship named for Eto nurse (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Army Information Branch, Information and Education Division (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Various Memoranda (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Victory in Burma (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Army Clip Sheet (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Officer Roster (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Various Memoranda (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Grace Kempton Outgoing Memoranda 1944-1945 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Washington Post October 21, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Personal Affairs Directory 1 July 1944 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Various Articles (Box 18, Folder 12)
- English-Speaking Civilians 'Shock' to WAC Back from Italy (Box 18, Folder 13)
- War Department Bureau of Public Relations (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Various Articles (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous Material (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Camp Davis by the Sea (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Recruiters Review (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous Material (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Jumpin' Jupiter (Box 18, Folder 20)
- War Review by the Under Secretary of War (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Memoranda (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Tuscaloosa, Alabama (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Memorandum to Major Mitchell (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Various Poems (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Rough Draft (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Verses and Phrases for Armed Forces Radio Services (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Feature Material (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Miscellaneous Material (Box 18, Folders 29-30)
- A Few Quick Facts (Box 18, Folder 31)
- Get your education Under GI Bill of Rights (Box 18, Folder 32)
- More Job Possibilities (Box 18, Folder 33)
- Map of Japan (Box 18, Folder 34)
- Map (Box 18, Folder 35)
- Geneology: Kempton & Akkington (Box 18, Folder 36)
- Going back to Civilian Life (Box 18, Folder 37)
- Continuance of National Service Life Insurance (Box 19, Folder 1)
- The Story of American-Russian Friendship (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Code of Wartime Practices June 15, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- He's Back (Box 19, Folder 4)
- What the Soldier Thinks (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Yokel Issue Put Out by Prop Wash January 1945 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Activities of the New York Branch Office Information & Education Division (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Outfit 15 Jan. 1945 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Recruiters Review (Box 19, Folder 9)
- What the Soldier Thinks (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Army Talk Publications (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Seperation Counseling Bulletin (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Morale Program Atlanta 3, Georgia (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Digest (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Bulletin of Information Women's Interest Section (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Recruiters Review (Box 19, Folder 16)
- "Now is the Time" Number One by Priscilla Kent Manuscript (Box 19, Folder 17)
- The Kennedian Sept. 1944 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Radio Branch Bureau of Public Relations (Box 19, Folder 19)
- War Department Bureau of Public Relations Press Branch (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Graduation 48th Officer Candidate Class of the Women's Army Corps February 1944 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Basic Field Manual Military Courtesy and Discipline June 15, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Pocket Guide to China (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Officer Qualifications Record (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Army Service Forces Position Description Questionnaire (Box 19, Folder 25)
- At Ease (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Telephone Directory (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Telephone Directory November 9, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- GK Why I joined the Army (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Physical Training (Box 19, Folder 30)
- War Department Bureau of Officers (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Miscellaneous Material (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Procurement of Female Technicians for Medical Installations (Box 19, Folder 33)
- William F. Polk Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 34)
- The American Mercury (Box 19, Folder 35)
- Various Propaganda (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Giloth Negatives (Box 20, Folder 2)
- British Information Services (Box 20, Folder 3)
- War Week (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Journalism Quarterly (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Guide to the Use of Information Materials (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Cooking Guide (Box 20, Folder 7)
- The Matrix Publication (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Recruiters Review (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Helen Pagel Negatives (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Office Material (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Germany (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Office for Emergency Management (Box 20, Folder 13)
- The Best from Yank the Army Weekly (Box 20, Folder 14)
- USO - United Service Organization (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Women's Radio War Program Guide June 1944 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Yank: The Army Weekly - June 30 Vol. 3 No. 2 1944 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Book: You can Survive Atomic Attack by: Willard F. Libby, Ph.D. (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Propaganda for War - The Campaign Against American Neutrality By: H.C. Peterson (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Book: Propaganda for Democracy by Paul Garrett (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Booklet: Enemy Japan - prepared by the Office of War Information (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Picture Article: The Proudest Title in the Army (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Articles: Vinegar Joe's 'Match' Leaves for Overseas (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Article: You can do this Job and Release A man to fight! (Box 21, Folder 8)
- News of Women's Activities in War, Club and Home: Majoring in Peas, WACS in Africa Hope for Tovagner Jobs, It's a Woman's War (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Article: The Spirit that won the army (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Battery General Hospital: Dedicated to our Brave fighting men who are giving their all that we may continue a free America! (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Newspaper Clipping (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Army Life: United States Army Recruiting News: Newly Appointed Director of the Women's Army Corps (Box 21, Folder 13)
- The Saturday Evening Post: All for the Love of a Lady (January 8, 1944) (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Supply - 1943 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Public Speaking (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Public Relations (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Medicine (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Physical Training (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Organization of the Army (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Military Sanitation and First Aid (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Military Law and Cour Martial Procedures (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Methods of Training (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Manners and Customs (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Duties and Resp. of O.F.F. (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Memorandum Carrier Sheet (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Grace Kempton Discharge Papers (Box 21, Folder 27)
- War Ration Books (Box 21, Folder 28)
- WAC Newsletter (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Infantry Drill Regulations Aug. 4, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Weekly Schedule of Instruction for Forty-eighth Candidate Class (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Department of the Interior (Box 21, Folder 32)
- War Propaganda (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Women's Army Corps Song Book 1 August 1944 (Box 21, Folder 34)
- Office of War Information (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Delegates and officials of the United Nations Conference on International Organization 1945 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Information About the WAAC (Box 22, Folder 3)
- List of Officer Candidates in the WAAC (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Table of Basic Allowances - War Department Women's Army Auxiliary Corps (Chemical equipment list) (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Table of Organization and Equipment No. 10-57 Truck Company, QuarterMaster Battallon (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Table of Equipment No. 21 - Clothing & Individual Equipment (extract) (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Supply Statement & Letter + Report of Survey (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Post Card - Gas Drill, Third WAAC Training Center (Oglethorpe, GA. near Chattanooga, Tenn.) (Box 22, Folder 9)
- The Evening Star - Reunion in Australia (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Hammond Becomes Price Check Here - Rome, Georgia (Monday, March 6, 1944) (Box 22, Folder 11)
- War Times, Washington. D.C. February 9, 1945 (Frowning Army Censor Tries to Scowl the General Down) (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Article Lt. Arrington Completes 87 Combat Missions in Europe (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Article: Capt. W.W. Wyatt killed in Action (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Article: Miss McAfee Bids Civilian Men to be Hosts to Service Women (Hearld Tribune Bureau) (Box 22, Folder 15)
- The Atlanta Constitution - can supply Need for WAACS Greater than Army Recruiters Atlanta, GA Sunday Morning, April 18, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- News from Germany - December 1939 Nos. 27/28 (issued by H.R. Hoffmann, Starnberg, Bavaria, Germany) (Box 22, Folder 17)
- American Views - December 1939 No. 3 (Supplement to "News from Germany" Nos. 27/28, 1939) (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Various Propaganda (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Yay Material (Box 22, Folder 20)
- North Beach Material (Box 22, Folder 21)
- The Separator (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Public Relations Branch (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Broadcasting (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Various Postcards (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous Material (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Notes Oct. 15 - Nov. 4, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Weekly Summary of News Clippings (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Miscellaneous Material (Box 22, Folders 29-30)
- The Matrix Publication (Box 22, Folder 31)
- OWI Radio (Box 23, Folder 1)
- 1943 Plans and Policies Domestic Radio Bureau Office of War Information Washington, D.C. (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Radio Material (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Yank (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Material (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Photograph (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Photographs June 21, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Various Photographs (Box 23, Folders 8-11)
- Army Newspaper Editor's Manual (Box 23, Folder 12)
- WAC Personal Material (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Recruiting Conference for the Women's Army Corps March 1944 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Broadcasters' Wartime (Box 23, Folder 15)
- United Mine Workers of America (Box 23, Folder 16)
- What the Soldier thinks (Box 23, Folders 17-20)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Newspaper Clipping (Photos) (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Various Newspaper Clippings (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Picture for Grace from Bob (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Various Photographs (Box 24, Folders 4-9)
- Miscellaneous Manuscripts (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous Material (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Constitution of the Junior Assembly (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Mileage Rationing Record (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Program of Ceremonies April 12, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Certificate of Meritorious Service awarded to Grace Kempton (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Graduation Forty-Eighth Officer Candidate Class of the Women's Army Corps February 1944 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous Material (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Georgia Press Institute February 18-21, 1942 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous Manuscript (Box 24, Folder 19)
- An Autobiography by Grace Kempton (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Graduation Twenty-eighth officer candidate Class of the Women's Army Auxiliary Corps May 17, 1943 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous Material (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Occupation May Japan and the Far East (Box 24, Folder 23)
- WAC Recruiting Conference Fourth Service Command 27 July 1944 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Newspaper Clippings (Box 24, Folders 25-29)
- Miscellaneous Material (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Mileage Voucher (Box 24, Folder 31)
- Western Union Telegrams for Grace Kempton (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Bachelor Party Letter/Invitation (Box 24, Folder 33)
- A Short Guide to Iraq (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Swedish Language Guide (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Italian Language Guide (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Icelandic Language Guide (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Pocket Guide to West Africa (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Pocket Guide to France (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Hindustani Language Guide (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Tagalog Language Guide (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Pocket Guide to Germany (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Portuguese Language Guide (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Italian Language Guide (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Pocket Guide to China (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Thai (Siamese) Language Guide (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Norwegian Language Guide (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Malay Language Guide (Box 25, Folder 15)
- North African Arabic Language Guide (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Pocket Guide to Netherlands East Indies (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Solution in Asia The Infantry Journal (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Attack! (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Albanian Language Guide (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Japanese Language Guide (Box 25, Folder 21)
- A Short Guide to Syria (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Pocket Guide to Iran (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Pocket Guide to New Caledonia (Box 26, Folder 2)
- A Pocket Guide to Alaska (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Rumanian Language Guide (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Pocket Guide to Japan (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Icelandic Language Guide (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Going back to Civilian life (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Pocket Guide to Italian Cities (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Pocket Guide to Paris And Cities of Northern France (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Pocket Guide to the Cities of Belgium and Luxembourg (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Russian Language Guide (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Pocket Guide to New Zealand (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Pocket Guide to the USSR (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Japanese Phrase Book (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Russian Language Guide (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Women's Army Corps Song Book August 1, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Pocket Guide to France (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Pocket Guide to Burma (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Pocket Guide to the Cities of Norway (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Pocket Guide to Northern Ireland (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Pocket Guide to Australia (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Person Language Guide (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Dutch Language Guide (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Pocket Guide to the Cities of Southern France (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Cantonese Language Guide (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Pocket Guide to the Cities of Denmark (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Japanese Language Guide (Box 27, Folder 3)
- War Map of Europe (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Photograph (Box 27, Folder 5)
- A Short Guide to Great Britain (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Turkish Language Guide (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Pocket Guide to Egypt (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Pocket Guide to the Cities of Southern France (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Pocket Guide to Paris and Cities of Northern France (Box 27, Folder 10)
- German Language Guide (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Greek Language Guide (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Pocket Guide to Italian Cities (Box 27, Folder 13)
- A Pocket Guide to New Guinea (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Hungarian Language Guide (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Portuguese Language Guide (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Bulgarian Language Guide (Box 27, Folder 17)
- German Language Guide (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Serbo-Croatian Language Guide (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Women's Army Corps Song Book 1 August 1944 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Danish Language Guide (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Burmese Language Guide (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Outgoing Correspondence from Willett Kempton (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Willett Kempton Incoming Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Incoming Correspondence to Willett Kempton (Box 28, Folder 3)
- United Nations Conference on International Organization for the Press (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Various Notes (Box 28, Folder 5)
- List for Hamilton Field - June 25, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- List for Signing of Charter Veteran's Auditorium June 25, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Supplement to the Press, Periodical, Radio and Newsphotographic Directory (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Various Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 9)
- KPO-NBC Service June 27, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous Material (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Willett Kempton Material (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Press-Radio Relations Office Memorandum (Box 28, Folder 13)
- The United Nations Conference on International Organization Plenary (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Order of the Day The United Nations Conference on International Organization (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous Material (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Various Telegrams (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Various Materials (Box 28, Folder 18)
- The United Nations Conference on International Organization Commission I and III (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Incoming Correspondence to Frank McCall (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Incoming Correspondence to John A. Sutro (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Incoming Correspondence to M.J. MacDermott (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Incoming Correspondence to Harold McGrath (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Incoming Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Delegates and Officials of the United Nations Conference on International Organization San Francisco, California 1945 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- The Baha'I Peace Program (Box 28, Folder 27)
- Guide the United Nations Conference on International Organization San Francisco 1945 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- United Nations Theatre San Francisco 1945 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- The United Nations Conference on International Organization June 25, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- United Nations of the World May 23, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- The United Nations Conference on International Organization April 25, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 32)
- Program Closing Plenary Session June 26, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 33)
- Within the Golden Gate (Box 28, Folder 34)
- Organizational Telephone Directory August 1945 (Box 28, Folder 35)
- Directory San Francisco California May 1, 1945 (Box 28, Folders 36-37)
- Willet Kempton Incoming Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 1)
- French Language Guide (Box 29, Folder 2)
- I & E Digest (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Hints on News Reporting Murray Sheehan (Box 29, Folder 4)
- The Automobile User's Guide with Wartime Suggestions (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Spoken Italian (Box 29, Folder 6)
- The Battle is the Pay-Off by: Captain Ralph Ingersoll (Box 29, Folder 7)
- A Manual for Courts - Martial U.S. Army 1928 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Sex Hygiene Course: Officers and Officer Candidates Womens Army Auxiliary Corps, May 27,1943. Restricted - War Department - Pamphlet No. 35-1 [Found inside "A Manual for Courts-Martial U.S. Army, 1928"] (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Chile land of Contrasts (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Brazilian Introduction to a Neighbor (Box 29, Folder 10)
- The U.S.S.R. The Institutions & People (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Army Life (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Sword of Freedom (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Application for Federal Employment (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Office of War Information (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous Material (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Various Clippings (Box 29, Folder 17)
- WAC News Letter (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Overseas Woman April-May 1945 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Overseas Woman June 1945 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Overseas Woman July - September 1945 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Overseas Woman October - November 1945 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Overseas Woman December 1945 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Various Propaganda (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Home Front (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Material (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Conference United States Army Recruiting Officers (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous Material (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous Clippings (Box 30, Folders 12-14)
- Yank Newspaper (Flat-box 31, Folders 1-5)
- Yank Newspaper (Flat-box 32, Folders 1-5)
- Yank Newspaper (Flat-box 33, Folders 1-3)
- Yank Newspaper (Flat-box 34, Folders 1-6)
- The Home Front 1942-1943 (Flat-box 36, Folders 1-5)
- Scrapbook [loose clippings and other ephemera] (Flat-box 38, Item 1)
- Various Newspapers (Flat-box 35, Folders 1-5)
- Maps (Flat-box 37, Folders 1-9)
- Ephemera [matchbooks, patches, etc.] (Flat-box 39, Item 1)
- Yank magazine, 1944-11-1945-06 (Flat-box 40, Folders 1-8)
- San Francisco Scoop, 1945-05-20 (Flat-box 40, Folder 9)
- WAC article drafts, notes re: Oak Ridge/Manhattan Project, 1945 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- WAC administrative forms, notes, reports, 1943 (Box 41, Folders 2-3)
- WAC article drafts, 1944 (Box 41, Folders 4-5)
- WAC Overseas press releases, memos & article drafts (Box 41, Folders 6-7)
- WAC Overseas press releases, memos & article drafts, 1944 (Box 41, Folders 8-9)
- WAC Overseas press releases, memos & article drafts, 1945 (Box 41, Folders 10)
- WAC articles, drafts, & press releases, 1944-1945 (Box 41, Folders 11-12)
- Miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 13)
- United Nations conference memos, correspondence, etc., 1945 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Bureau of Public Relations, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- War Review by the Secretary of War press releases, 1944-1945 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Report on Universal Military Training, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Radio script: Be Your Own Censor (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Home Front article clippings, 1942-1943 (Box 42, Folders 5-7)
- Newspaper clippings, Answers to Your War Questions column etc., 1942 (Box 42, Folders 8-9)
- Office of Emergency Management Division of Information: Answers to Your War Questions releases, 1942 (Box 42, Folders 10)
- Home Front clippings (Box 42, Folder 11)
- UN conference internal memos, lists, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Round the World WAC Round-Up, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- WAC biographical profiles (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Bureau of Public Relations press releases, 1945 (Box 42, Folders 15-16)
- WAC recruitment poster (Box 42, Folder 17)
- WAC News, clippings of comics, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Main family tree (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Lord & Thomas Advertising & Merchandising Map, 1942 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Sheet music (Box 42, Folder 21)
- clipping, The Palm, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- War Production News, teletype message (Box 43, Folder 2)
- The Home Front press releases and graphics (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Willet Kempton incoming correspondence, 1943 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- War Questions clippings, 1942-06 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Home Front clippings, 1943 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- WAC Third Training Center, Fort Oglethorpe, Georgia (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Office for Emergency Management radio scripts, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- WAC Backgound: Editorials, Quotes, Poems, etc. (Box 43, Folder 9)
- WAC clippings, drafts, press releases, etc. (Box 43, Folder 10)
- clippings re: UN conference, 1945 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- The Officer's Guide (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Article typescript drafts (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Stationery & routing slips (Box 44, Folder 2)
- War Departmernt memoranda & bulletins (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 44, Folders 4-6)
- Notes, personal documents & ephemera (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, etc., 1968-1972 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Photographs, 1968-1972 (Box 44, Folders 9-11)
- Booklets, directory, other printed matter, 1968-1972 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Ephemera (postcards, matchbooks, ration book, ID cards, etc.) (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Newspaper clippings (Box 45, Folders 2-5)
- G.I. Gripes, 1945 (Box 45, Folders 3-5)
  Scope and Contents
  Internal documents quoting GIs' candid criticisms expressed during discussions sponsored by the Information & Education Branch.
- Clippings etc. by or about the Kemptons (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Newspaper clippings - oversize (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Newsmap Vol.4 No. 14F (Army Information Branch), July 23, 1945 (Map-folder 47)